Register of the William H. Rehnquist papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings, 1971-2005
  - Constitutional Address, Dickinson College and Dickinson School of Law, Pennsylvania State University, Carlisle, Pennsylvania, 1999 November 12 (Box-folder 254: 3)
  - Remarks, William H. Rehnquist Award for Judicial Excellence presentation, National Center for State Courts dinner, Washington, D.C., 1999 November 15. Typescript and correspondence (Box-folder 254: 4)
  - Civil Liberties in Wartime, speech, Director's Forum, Woodrow Wilson Center, Washington, D.C., 1999 November 17 (Box-folder 254: 5)
  - Remarks, Opperman House opening ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1999 November 18 (Box-folder 254: 6)
  - The American Constitutional Experience: Stress and Strain among the Three Branches of Government, Tampa Bay Chapter of the Federal Bar Association meeting, Tampa Bay, Florida, 1999 December 11 (Box-folder 255: 1)
    Typescript, transcript, clippings, and correspondence
  - Remarks, James Smithson Medal presentation, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C., 1999 December 12 (Box-folder 255: 2)
  - Remarks, swearing-in ceremony, United States Sentencing Commission, Washington, D.C., 2000 January 5 (Box-folder 255: 3)
  - Remarks, installation of Larry Small as Secretary of the Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C., 2000 January 24 (Box-folder 255: 4)
  - Visiting lecturer, School of Law, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 2000 February 1-10 (Box-folder 255: 5)
  - Introductory remarks, Founders' Day Dinner, Washington, D.C., 2000 February 25 (Box-folder 255: 6)
  - Opening remarks, Democracy and the Rule of Law in a Changing World Order conference, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C., 2000 March 6 (Box-folder 256: 1)
  - Remarks, reception for Kathleen Sullivan, Washington, D.C., 2000 March 22 (Box-folder 256: 2)
  - Welcoming remarks, official visit of the European Court of Justice, Washington, D.C., 2000 April 19 (Box-folder 256: 3)
  - Speech, 100th anniversary celebration, Norfolk and Portsmouth Bar Association, Norfolk, Virginia, 2000 May 3 (Box-folder 256: 4)
  - Remarks, American Law Institute meeting, Washington, D.C., 2000 May 15 (Box-folder 256: 5)
  - Commencement address, George Washington University Law School, Washington, D.C., 2000 May 28 (Box-folder 256: 6)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Williamsburg, Virginia, 2000 June 16 (Box-folder 256: 7)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the Fourth Circuit, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 2000 July 1 (Box-folder 257: 1)
  - Visiting lecturer, St. Mary's University Summer Program, Innsbruck, Austria, 2000 July 3-12 (Box-folder 257: 2)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the Court of Appeals for Veterans Claims, Washington, D.C., 2000 September 18 (Box-folder 257: 3)
  - Remarks, Anglo-American Legal Exchange dinner, Washington, D.C., 2000 September 21 (Box-folder 257: 4)
  - Remarks, investiture of Timothy B. Dyk, Washington, D.C., 2000 September 26 (Box-folder 257: 5)
  - John Marshall, speech, School of Law, College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia, 2000 October 6 (Box-folder 257: 6)
  - Introductory remarks, Supreme Court Historical Society Lecture series, Washington, D.C., 2000 October 12 (Box-folder 257: 7)
  - Introductory remarks, Founders' Lecture Series, Washington Bar Association, Howard University, Washington, D.C., 2000 October 19 (Box-folder 257: 8)
  - Remarks, groundbreaking ceremony, Steven F. Udvar-Hazy Center, National Air and Space Museum, Washington Dulles International Airport, 2000 October 25 (Box-folder 257: 9)
  - Panel discussion, American College of Trial Lawyers meeting, Washington, D.C., 2000 October 28 (Box-folder 258: 1)
  - Remarks, National Center for State Courts luncheon, Washington, D.C., 2000 November 14 (Box-folder 258: 2)
  - Remarks, Bar Association of the District of Columbia banquet, Washington, D.C., 2000 December 2 (Box-folder 258: 3)
  - Remarks, United States Tax Court luncheon, Washington, D.C., 2000 December 13 (Box-folder 258: 4)
  - Remarks, John Carroll Society brunch, Washington, D.C., 2001 January 7 (Box-folder 258: 5)
  - Remarks, farewell for Seth Waxman and Barbara Underwood, Washington, D.C., 2001 January 18 (Box-folder 258: 6)
  - Visiting lecturer, School of Law, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 2001 January 30-February 9 (Box-folder 258: 7)
  - Remarks, Federal Judicial Pay Erosion White Paper presentation, Washington, D.C., 2001 February 13 (Box-folder 258: 8)
  - Interview, Charlie Rose program, Washington, D.C., 2001 February 14 (Box-folder 258: 9)
  - Remarks, farewell for Lyle Deniston, Washington, D.C., 2001 February 15 (Box-folder 258: 10)
  - Address, bicentennial celebration luncheon, Historical Society of the District of Columbia Circuit, Washington, D.C., 2001 March 9 (Box-folder 259: 1)
  - Remarks, conference on judicial compensation, Washington, D.C., 2001 March 13 (Box-folder 259: 2)
  - Remarks, Montpelier Foundation dinner, 2001 March 16 (Box-folder 259: 3)
  - Remarks, Metropolitan Club meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 April 6 (Box-folder 259: 4)
  - Remarks, Swedish Colonial Society luncheon, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 2001 April 9 (Box-folder 259: 5)
  - Remarks, bicentennial banquet, Arlington Historical Society, 2001 April 27 (Box-folder 259: 6)
  - Remarks, Phi Delta Phi-Rehnquist Inn meeting, Suffolk University, Boston, Massachusetts, 2001 April 30 (Box-folder 259: 7)
  - Remarks, Federal Judges Association meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 May 8 (Box-folder 259: 8)
  - Opening remarks, American Law Institute meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 May 14 (Box-folder 259: 9)
  - Commencement address, Calvin College, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 2001 May 19 (Box-folder 259: 10)
    Typescript, print, and correspondence
  - The Supreme Court in the Nineteenth Century, lecture, Supreme Court Historical Society meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 June 4 (Box-folder 260: 1)
  - Acceptance speech, Brien McMahon Award for Distinguished Public Service, Fordham University Club, Washington, D.C., 2001 June 11 (Box-folder 260: 2)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the Fourth Circuit, Hot Springs, Virginia, 2001 June 30 (Box-folder 260: 3)
  - Visiting lecturer, Dickinson School of Law Summer Program, Strasbourg, France, 2001 July 2-12 (Box-folder 260: 4)
  - Remarks, Faculty of Law, University of Guanajuato, Guanajuato, Mexico, 2001 September 27 (Box-folder 260: 5)
  - Introductory remarks, Supreme Court Historical Society lecture series, Washington, D.C., 2001 October 11 (Box-folder 260: 6)
  - Remarks, American Meteorological Society meeting, 2001 October 23 (Box-folder 261: 1)
  - The Future of the Federal Courts, speech, University of Virginia School of Law, Charlottesville, Virginia, 2001 October 27 (Box-folder 261: 2)
  - Veterans Day Invocation, Salute to Veterans Committee dinner, Washington, D.C., 2001 November 8 (Box-folder 261: 3)
  - Remarks, William H. Rehnquist Award for Judicial Excellence Award presentation, National Center for State Courts Dinner, Washington, D.C., 2001 November 15 (Box-folder 261: 4)
  - Visiting lecturer, School of Law, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 2002 January 28-February 8 (Box-folder 261: 5)
  - Remarks, farewell for Gail Galloway, Washington, D.C., 2002 February 28 (Box-folder 261: 6)
  - Remarks, George Mason National Memorial dedication ceremony, Washington, D.C., 2002 April 9 (Box-folder 261: 7)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit, Washington, D.C., 2002 April 8 (Box-folder 261: 8)
  - Remarks, groundbreaking ceremony, E. Barrett Prettyman Courthouse Annex, Washington, D.C., 2002 April 8 (Box-folder 261: 9)
  - Lecture, My Life in the Law series, Duke University School of Law, Durham, North Carolina, 2002 April 13 (Box-folder 262: 1)
  - Remarks, 50th anniversary of DACOR (Diplomats and Consular Officers Retired) Bacon House, Washington, D.C., 2002 April 19 (Box-folder 262: 2)
  - Remarks, public reading, Center for the Book, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C., 2002 May 1 (Box-folder 262: 3)
  - Commencement address, Marymount University, Arlington, Virginia, 2002 May 12 (Box-folder 262: 4)
  - Acceptance speech, Tradition of Excellence Award presentation, Shorewood High School, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2002 May 24 (Box-folder 262: 5)
  - Dinner hosted by the Chief Justice, Supreme Court, Washington, D.C., 2002 June 12 (Box-folder 262: 6)
  - Panel discussion, Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Williamsburg, Virginia, 2002 June 14 (Box-folder 263: 1)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the Fourth Circuit, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 2002 June 29 (Box-folder 263: 2)
  - Visiting lecturer, Dickinson School of Law Summer Program, Strasbourg, France, 2002 July 2-10 (Box-folder 263: 3)
  - Testimony, National Commission on the Public Service meeting, Washington, D.C., 2002 July 15 (Box-folder 263: 4)
  - Remarks, National Association of Former United States Attorneys meeting, Washington, D.C., 2002 September 7 (Box-folder 263: 5)
  - Remarks, Notre Dame Law School, Notre Dame, Indiana, 2002 September 13 (Box-folder 263: 6)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference luncheon in honor of Charles Haden, Washington, D.C., 2002 September 24 (Box-folder 264: 1)
  - Remarks, Treasures of Ancient Egypt exhibit opening, National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C., 2002 September 24 (Box-folder 264: 2)
  - Remarks, Andrew W. Mellon dinner, National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C., 2002 September 25 (Box-folder 264: 3)
  - Foreword to biography of Robert H. Jackson, 2002 October 9 (Box-folder 264: 4)
  - Presidential Power in Times of Crisis: The Steel Seizure Case Revisited, program presented as part of the 50th reunion of the Class of 1952, Stanford Law School, Stanford University, Stanford, California, 2002 October 18 (Box-folder 264: 5)
  - Opening remarks, National Symposium for United States Court of Appeals Judges, Federal Judicial Center, Washington, D.C., 2002 October 21 (Box-folder 264: 6)
  - Remarks, William H. Rehnquist Award for Judicial Excellence Award presentation, National Center for State Courts Dinner, Washington, D.C., 2002 October 24 (Box-folder 264: 7)
  - President Truman and the Steel Seizure Case: A Fifty Year Retrospective, videotaped introduction to symposium, School of Law, Duquesne University, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 2002 November 22 (Box-folder 264: 8)
    Transcript, printed copy, and correspondence
  - Remarks, official visit by delegation from the French Cour de Cassation, Washington, D.C., 2002 November 4 (Box-folder 265: 1)
  - Invocation, Salute to Veterans dinner, University Club, Washington, D.C., 2002 November 7 (Box-folder 265: 2)
  - Albritton Lecture, University of Alabama, Tuscaloosa, Alabama, 2002 November 22 (Box-folder 265: 3)
    (cancelled appearance). Typescript and correspondence
  - Visit to the White House, Washington, D.C., 2002 December 20 (Box-folder 265: 4)
  - Remarks, Thurgood Marshall stamp ceremony, Washington, D.C., 2003 January 7 (Box-folder 265: 5)
  - Visiting lecturer, School of Law, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 2003 February 3-14 (Box-folder 265: 6)
  - Remarks, Supreme Court Fellows Program dinner, Washington, D.C., 2003 February 21 (Box-folder 265: 7)
  - Judicial Independence, speech, Allen Chair Symposium on Independence of the Judiciary, T. C. Williams School of Law, University of Richmond, Virginia, 2003 March 21 (Box-folder 266: 1)
  - Stanford Law School Class of 1952 reunion dinner, Washington, D.C., 2003 March 29 (Box-folder 266: 2)
  - Henry J. Abraham Lecture, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, 2003 April 11 (Box-folder 266: 3)
  - Reviewing Rehnquist, article by Richard Brust, ABA Journal, 2003 May (Box-folder 266: 4)
    Printed copy and photographs
  - Remarks, Board of Directors meeting, Federal Judges Association, Washington, D.C., 2003 May 5 (Box-folder 266: 5)
  - Remarks, Robert H. Jackson Center dedication ceremony, Jamestown, New York, 2003 May 16 (Box-folder 267: 1)
    Typescript, clippings, print, and correspondence
  - Interview for program on John Marshall, 2003 May 22 (Box-folder 267: 2)
  - Statement, Federal Judicial Pay White Paper presentation, Washington, D.C., 2003 May 28 (Box-folder 267: 3)
  - Remarks, groundbreaking ceremony, Supreme Court Building renovation, Washington, D.C., 2003 June 17 (Box-folder 267: 4)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the Fourth Circuit, 2003 June 28 (Box-folder 267: 5)
  - Visiting lecturer, St. Mary's School of Law Summer Program, Innsbruck, Austria, 2003 July 7-15 (Box-folder 267: 6)
    (cancelled). Correspondence only
  - Remarks, First Responders Cup Tournament, Arlington Girls Softball Association, Arlington, Virginia, 2003 September 13 (Box-folder 268: 1)
  - Remarks, Rotunda of the Charters of Freedom rededication ceremony, National Archives, Washington, D.C., 2003 September 17 (Box-folder 268: 2)
  - Presentation, Redeemer Lutheran Church, McLean, Virginia, 2003 September 30 (Box-folder 268: 3)
  - 2003 Albritton Lecture: The Supreme Court and the Disputed Election of 1876, Albritton Lecture Series, University of Alabama School of Law, Tuscaloosa, Alabama, 2003 October 24 (Box-folder 268: 4)
  - Salute to Veterans dinner, University Club, Washington, D.C., 2003 November 11 (Box-folder 268: 5)
  - Remarks, Dual Enforcement of Constitutional Norms conference, Institute of Bill of Rights Law and National Center for State Courts, Williamsburg, Virginia, 2003 November 14 (Box-folder 268: 6)
  - Remarks, National Center for State Courts luncheon, Washington, D.C., 2003 November 21 (Box-folder 268: 7)
  - Remarks, Steven F. Udvar-Hazy Center dedication ceremony, National Air and Space Museum, Chantilly, Virginia, 2003 December 11 (Box-folder 268: 8)
  - Visiting lecturer, School of Law, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 2004 February 2-14 (Box-folder 268: 9)
  - Acceptance speech, Public Service Award presentation, University of Arizona Alumni Association, Tucson, Arizona, 2004 February 10 (Box-folder 269: 1)
  - Introductory remarks, David Frederick lecture, Supreme Court Historical Society Lecture Series, Washington, D.C., 2004 February 19 (Box-folder 269: 2)
  - Remarks, Founders' Day Dinner, University Club, Washington, D.C., 2004 February 21 (Box-folder 269: 3)
  - Testimony, John Marshall Commemorative Coin Act hearing, Subcommittee on Domestic and International Monetary Policy, House of Representatives, Washington, D.C., 2004 March 10 (Box-folder 269: 4)
  - Remarks, Roger Brooke Taney House and Museum rededication ceremony, Historical Society of Frederick County, Frederick, Maryland, 2004 April 7 (Box-folder 269: 5)
  - Remarks, Metropolitan Club literary luncheon, 2004 April 15 (Box-folder 269: 6)
  - Acceptance speech, Distinguished Washingtonian Award presentation, University Club, Washington, D.C., 2004 April 22 (Box-folder 269: 7)
  - Remarks, Ohio Judicial Center dedication ceremony, Columbus, Ohio, 2004 May 15 (Box-folder 269: 8)
  - Remarks, American Law Institute Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2004 May 17 (Box-folder 269: 9)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference luncheon, United States Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court, Washington, D.C., 2004 May 18 (Box-folder 269: 10)
  - Congressional Judicial Caucus reception, Washington, D.C., 2004 May 20 (Box-folder 270: 1)
  - Remarks, Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Hot Springs, Virginia, 2004 June 17 (Box-folder 270: 2)
  - Visiting lecturer, Tulane University Summer Program, Cambridge, England, July 6-14 (Box-folder 270: 3)
  - 1984, review of book by George Orwell, Michigan Law Review, 2004 August 24 (Box-folder 270: 4)
  - Remarks, farewell for Ted Olson, Washington, D.C., 2004 September 14 (Box-folder 270: 5)
  - Canadian/American Legal Exchange, Ottawa, Canada, 2004 September 28-October 1 (Box-folder 270: 6)
  - Remarks, University of Nebraska Law School, Lincoln, Nebraska, 2004 October 29 (Box-folder 270: 7)
  - Visiting lecturer, School of Law, University of Arizona, Tucson, Arizona, 2005 February 1-11 (Box-folder 270: 8)
  - Remarks,250th anniversary celebration of John Marshall's birth, Richmond, Virginia, 2005 April 30 (Box-folder 270: 9)
- Invitations, 1971-2005
  Consists of invitations, correspondence, notes, event checklists, guest lists, menus, souvenirs, and photographs relating to events (both official Supreme Court functions and informal social occasions) to which Rehnquist was invited. Arranged in two subseries: Accepted, 1985-2003, and Declined, 1971-2005.
  - Accepted, 1985-2003
    Consists of invitations, correspondence, notes, event checklists, guest lists, menus, souvenirs, and photographs relating to events attended by the Chief Justice. Documents official Supreme Court functions in addition to informal social occasions. Provides documentation of the Chief Justice's social circle, daily activities, hobbies, and the role of the Court among U.S. and international law community. Arranged in chronological order by the date the event was held. The months of July and August are absent for most years, since the court was not sitting during those months. Gaps in the collection exist for the months of September-December 1989, May-December 1991, June-October 1992, and June 1999
    - 1985 September-October (Box-folder 271: 1)
    - 1985 October (Box-folder 271: 2)
    - 1985 October-December (Box-folder 271: 3)
    - 1986 January (Box-folder 271: 4)
    - 1986 February-April (Box-folder 271: 5)
    - 1986 April-May (Box-folder 271: 6)
    - 1986 June (Box-folder 271: 7)
    - 1986 September-October (Box-folder 271: 8-9)
    - 1986 October- November (Box-folder 271: 10)
    - 1986 December (Box-folder 272: 1)
    - 1987 January-February (Box-folder 272: 2)
    - 1987 March (Box-folder 272: 3)
    - 1987 April (Box-folder 272: 4)
    - 1987 May (Box-folder 272: 5)
    - 1987 June (Box-folder 272: 6-7)
    - Tentative 1986 October Term (Box-folder 272: 8)
    - Tentative 1986 October Term, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 273: 1-2)
    - 1988 November (Box-folder 273: 3)
    - 1989 January (Box-folder 273: 4-5)
    - 1989 February (Box-folder 274: 1)
    - 1989 March (Box-folder 274: 2)
    - 1989 April (Box-folder 274: 3)
    - 1989 May (Box-folder 274: 4-6)
    - 1989 June (Box-folder 274: 7-9)
    - 1989 July (Box-folder 274: 10)
    - 1990 January (Box-folder 275: 1-3)
    - 1990 February (Box-folder 275: 4)
    - 1990 March (Box-folder 275: 5-6)
    - 1990 April (Box-folder 275: 7)
    - 1990 May (Box-folder 275: 9-10)
    - 1990 June (Box-folder 275: 10)
    - 1990 September (Box-folder 275: 11)
    - 1990 October (Box-folder 276: 1)
    - 1990 November (Box-folder 276: 2)
    - 1990 December (Box-folder 276: 3)
    - 1991 January (Box-folder 276: 4-5)
    - 1991 February (Box-folder 276: 6)
    - 1991 March (Box-folder 276: 7-8)
    - 1991 April (Box-folder 276: 9)
    - 1992 January (Box-folder 276: 10)
    - 1992 January (Box-folder 277: 1)
    - 1992 February (Box-folder 277: 2)
    - 1992 March (Box-folder 277: 3-4)
    - 1992 April (Box-folder 277: 5)
    - 1992 May (Box-folder 277: 6-7)
    - 1992 November (Box-folder 277: 8-9)
    - 1992 December (Box-folder 277: 10)
    - 1993 January (Box-folder 278: 1-2)
    - 1993 February (Box-folder 278: 3-4)
    - 1993 March (Box-folder 278: 5)
    - 1993 April (Box-folder 278: 6)
    - 1993 May (Box-folder 278: 7-8)
    - 1993 June (Box-folder 278: 9-10)
    - 1993 September (Box-folder 279: 1)
    - 1993 October (Box-folder 279: 2-3)
    - 1993 November (Box-folder 279: 4-5)
    - 1993 December (Box-folder 279: 6-7)
    - 1994 January (Box-folder 279: 8-9)
    - 1994 February (Box-folder 279: 10)
    - 1994 March (Box-folder 280: 1-3)
    - 1994 April (Box-folder 280: 4)
    - 1994 May (Box-folder 280: 5-7)
    - 1994 June (Box-folder 280: 8-9)
    - 1994 June (Box-folder 281: 1)
    - 1994 September (Box-folder 281: 2-3)
    - 1994 October (Box-folder 281: 4)
    - 1994 November (Box-folder 281: 5)
    - 1994 December (Box-folder 281: 6)
    - 1995 January (Box-folder 281: 7)
    - February 1995, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 281: 8)
    - 1995 March (Box-folder 281: 9)
    - 1995 April (Box-folder 281: 10)
    - 1995 May (Box-folder 282: 1-2)
    - 1995 June (Box-folder 282: 3-4)
    - 1995 September (Box-folder 282: 5)
    - 1995 October (Box-folder 282: 6)
    - November 1995 (Box-folder 282: 7)
    - 1995 December (Box-folder 282: 8)
    - 1996 January (Box-folder 282: 9)
    - 1996 February (Box-folder 282: 10)
    - 1996 March (Box-folder 282: 11)
    - 1996 April (Box-folder 283: 1)
    - 1996 May (Box-folder 283: 2)
    - 1996 June (Box-folder 283: 3-4)
    - 1996 September (Box-folder 283: 5-6)
    - 1996 October (Box-folder 283: 7)
    - 1996 November (Box-folder 283: 8)
    - 1996 December (Box-folder 283: 9)
    - 1997 January (Box-folder 283: 10)
    - 1997 February (Box-folder 283: 11)
    - 1997 March (Box-folder 284: 1)
    - 1997 April (Box-folder 284: 2-3)
    - 1997 May (Box-folder 284: 4)
    - 1997 June (Box-folder 284: 5-6)
    - 1997 July (Box-folder 284: 7)
    - 1997 September (Box-folder 284: 8-9)
    - 1997 October (Box-folder 284: 9-10)
    - 1997 November (Box-folder 285: 1)
    - 1997 December (Box-folder 285: 2)
    - 1998 January (Box-folder 285: 3-4)
    - 1998 February-March (Box-folder 285: 5)
    - 1998 March (Box-folder 285: 6)
    - 1998 April (Box-folder 285: 7-8)
    - 1998 May (Box-folder 285: 9-10)
    - 1998 June (Box-folder 285: 11)
    - 1998 June (Box-folder 286: 1)
    - 1998 September (Box-folder 286: 2-3)
    - 1998 October (Box-folder 286: 4-5)
    - 1998 November (Box-folder 286: 6)
    - 1998 December (Box-folder 286: 7)
    - 1999 January (Box-folder 286: 8)
    - 1999 February-March (Box-folder 286: 9)
    - 1999 April (Box-folder 287: 1-2)
    - 1999 May (Box-folder 287: 3-4)
    - 1999 September (Box-folder 287: 5-7)
    - 1999 October (Box-folder 287: 8-9)
    - 1999 November (Box-folder 288: 1-2)
    - 1999 December (Box-folder 288: 3)
    - 2000 January (Box-folder 288: 4)
    - 2000 February (Box-folder 288: 5)
    - 2000 March (Box-folder 288: 6-9)
    - 2000 April (Box-folder 288: 10)
    - 2000 May (Box-folder 289: 1-2)
    - 2000 June (Box-folder 289: 3-4)
    - 2000 September (Box-folder 289: 5-6)
    - 2000 October (Box-folder 289: 7)
    - 2000 November (Box-folder 289: 8)
    - 2000 December (Box-folder 289: 9)
    - 2001 January (Box-folder 289: 10)
    - 2001 February (Box-folder 290: 1)
    - 2001 March (Box-folder 290: 2-3)
    - 2001 April (Box-folder 290: 4)
    - 2001 May (Box-folder 290: 5-6)
    - 2001 June (Box-folder 290: 7)
    - 2001 September (Box-folder 290: 8)
    - 2001 October (Box-folder 290: 9)
    - 2001 November (Box-folder 290: 10)
    - 2001 December (Box-folder 290: 11)
    - 2002 January (Box-folder 291: 1-2)
    - 2002 February (Box-folder 291: 3)
    - 2002 March (Box-folder 291: 4-5)
    - 2002 April (Box-folder 291: 6)
    - 2002 May (Box-folder 291: 7-8)
    - 2002 June (Box-folder 291: 9-10)
    - 2002 September (Box-folder 292: 1)
    - 2002 October (Box-folder 292: 2-3)
    - 2002 November (Box-folder 292: 4)
    - 2002 December (Box-folder 292: 5)
    - 2003 January (Box-folder 292: 6-7)
    - 2003 February (Box-folder 292: 8)
    - 2003 March (Box-folder 292: 9)
    - 2003 April (Box-folder 293: 1)
    - 2003 May (Box-folder 293: 2-4)
    - 2003 June (Box-folder 293: 5-6)
    - 2003 September (Box-folder 293: 7)
    - 2003 October (Box-folder 293: 8-9)
    - 2003 November (Box-folder 294: 1-2)
    - 2003 December (Box-folder 294: 3)
  - Declined, 1971-2005